A Guide to the Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA274
Rockefeller Archive Center
Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty
1940s-1990s
Rockefeller Archive Center
Wang, Hao
FA274
75.12 Cubic Feet 169 document cases
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into six distinct series based on subject matter and media:
Series 1, Biographical Materials Series 2, Office Files Series 3, Manuscripts, Notes, and Notebooks Series 4, Reprints Series 5, Materials in Chinese Series 6, Audio-Visual and Miscellaneous Materials
Series 1, Biographical Materials, is arranged alphabetically, and includes information on Wang’s personal and academic life, including bibliographies, vita, biographical essays, and family correspondence.
Series 2, Office Files, is arranged alphabetically and is a hybrid of correspondence, subject files, and manuscripts (typically authored by others).
Series 3, Manuscripts, Notes, and Notebooks, is the largest series of material, and is also arranged alphabetically. This series consists of Wang’s notes, various drafts of manuscripts written by Wang (either for an article or book), as well as a set of research notebooks kept by Wang. Series 4, Reprints, is arranged alphabetically by reprint title; nearly all reprints are authored by Wang.
Series 5, Materials in Chinese, is arranged alphabetically, and consists of files whose contents were almost or entirely in Chinese. Folders in this series include manuscripts, notes, and correspondence.
Series 6, Audio-Visual and Miscellaneous Materials, includes three folders of photographs, one cassette tape, and two sets of a reprint index card catalog kept by Wang.
Related Materials
For related material on Wang's work, the researcher may wish to consult the following books in the Rockefeller Archive Center library:
Logic, Computers and Sets From Mathematics to Philosophy Beyond Analytic Philosophy: Doing Justice to What We Know Reflections on Kurt Gödel A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy
Biographical / Historical
Hao Wang was born on May 20, 1921 in Jinan (Tsinan) in what is today the People's Republic of China. Wang grew up in China, and received his Bachelor's degree in Mathematics from the National Southwestern Associated University in 1943, and his Master's degree in Philosophy from Tsing Hua University in 1945.
Wang moved to the United States, and in 1948, he received his Ph.D. in Philosophy from Harvard University. He remained at Harvard as a Junior Fellow of the Society of Fellows (from 1948 to 1951) and was subsequently appointed as Assistant Professor of Philosophy.
In 1954, Wang travelled to England, where he served as John Locke Lecturer and as Reader in the Philosophy of Mathematics (1956-1961) at Oxford University. Upon reentry into the United States, Wang treturned to Harvard as Gordon McKay Professor of Mathematical Logic and Applied Mathematics. During his tenure at Harvard, Wang also collaborated with the Burroughs Corporation, the University of Michigan, the International Business Machine Corporation (IBM), Bell Laboratories, and the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT).
In 1967, Wang joined the faculty of the Rockefeller University, a position he would hold until his death. Although the Logic Research Group was disbanded in 1976, Wang remained at the University, continuing his research and work in mathematics, logic, and philosophy. Wang's early research was in computer science, artificial intelligence, and automated theorem proving, and in the 1960s, he introduced domino problems ("Wang tiles"). Later in his career, Wang focused his attention on the life and writings of the mathematician-philosopher Kurt Gödel. Prior to his death in 1978, Gödel allowed Wang to have many in-depth discussions with him; one product of these conversations was Wang's 1987 book "Reflections on Kurt Gödel."
Wang was a member of the Association of Symbolic Logic and the American Academy of Arts and Sciences. He was named Honorary Professor at both Peking University (1985) and Tsing Hua University (1986). In addition to numerous articles, Wang authored "Logic, Computers and Sets" (1962), "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (1974), "Popular Lectures on Mathematical Logic" (1981), "Beyond Analytic Philosophy: Doing Justice to What We Know" (1985), and "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (1996). In 1983, Wang was awarded the first Milestone Prize for Automated Theorem Proving.
Hao Wang died of lymphoma at the age of 73 on May 13, 1995.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for scholarly research with select materials restricted, as noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 450 W184
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Hao Wang Papers were acquired by the Rockefeller University/Rockefeller Archive Center in 1995 and 1996, with small additions to the collection received in 2005 and 2006.
Logic; Philosophy; Philosophy of mathematics and science; Artificial intelligence -- History; History of philosophy; Automated theorem proving; Mathematics; Wang, Hao; Wittgenstein, Ludwig; Gödel, Kurt
- Biographical Materials, 1
  Arrangement
  Series 1, Biographical Materials, is arranged alphabetically, and includes information on Wang's personal and academic life, including bibliographies, vita, biographical essays, and family correspondence.
  - Bibliography, 1944-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography - Vita (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Sketches (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with R. Hoon Wang, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Family Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Family Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Folder restricted - contains closed materials.
  - Hao Wang - Personal (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Medical Record (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Old Bibliography - Vita; Miscellaneous Notes (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Permit to Reenter the United States (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Personal (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Personal Letters (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Wang v. Chen (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Wang v. Wang (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Office Files, 2
  Series 2, Office Files, is arranged alphabetically and is a hybrid of correspondence, subject files, and manuscripts (typically those authored by others).
  - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - A (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Reuben Abel (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Account Book, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Account Book, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Account Book, 1984-1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Robert Ackermann (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Address Book/Notebook (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Addresses (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Adler's Foreign Books, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Advances in Information Systems Science (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Aerospace Corporation (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Vincent G. Allfrey (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, New Directions in the Philosophy of Mathematics, February 10-15, 1990 ("The Rightful Place of Mathematics in Philosophy"), Includes: "Aperiodicity and Contraints" Abstract, "To and From Philosophy - Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, New Orleans, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - American Mathematical Society (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - American Mathematical Society Abstract Forms (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - American Mathematical Society Meeting, "Aperiodicity and Order", October 20-21, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - American Mathematical Society (AMS) Special Session on Proof Theory - Proceedings (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - American Mathematical Society, Summer Institute, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - American Philosophical Society (APA) Radical Caucus, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - B.S. Anand (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Steve Andors (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Irving H. Anellis (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Richard B. Angell (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report and Bibliography - Laboratory Reports (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Annual Report and Bibliography - Laboratory Reports (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Anti-Vivisection Leaflet (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Appointment Books, 1947-1959 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Appointment Calendars, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Aristotle Conference, UNESCO, Paris, June 1-3, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Articles and Clippings on China (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Artisjus (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Larry Ashley (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Günter Asser (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Association for Symbolic Logic (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Association for Symbolic Logic, Annual Meeting, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - "Atlantic Community News" (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Jay Atlas (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - ATP Volume, American Mathematical Society Publication Guidelines (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - A.K. Auslin (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - B (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Jon Barwise (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Basil Blackwell, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Dieter Baur (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Daniel Bayer (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Daniel Bayer (Box 5, Folder 62A)
  - H.J. Becker (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - A.S. Beg (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Mirza A.B. Bég (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - "Behavioral and Brain Sciences" (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Beijing, December 13, 1973-January 4, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Bell Labs (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Ga'bor Belova'ri (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Paul Benacerraf (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Alan Berger (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Robert Berger (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - William Bevan (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - William Bex (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Biennial Greater Boston (Mass.) Logic Conference (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Akeel Bilgrami (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Garrett Birkhoff (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Max Black (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - W.W. Bledsoe (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Irene Bloom (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - R.P. Boas (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Publishers (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - M. Boffa (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Bogden and Quigley (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Herbert G. Bohnert (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Book Hunters (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Book Jackets (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Books in Progress (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - George Boolos (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Egon Börger (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Boringhieri (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Boston Colloquium (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Alan Brajnikoff (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - The British Academy (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - John Brockman (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Detlev W. Bronk (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Brooks, etc., 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Harvey Brooks (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - William Browder (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - John Bruer (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - G. Brutan (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Tie-Mei Bu (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Tie Mei Bu (Box 6, Folder 102A)
  - Budget, Explanatory Notes, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - George C. Bump (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Mario Bunge (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Bunker-Ramo Corporation (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - J.B. Burgess (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - John Burgess (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Hans Burkhardt (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Arthur W. Burks (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Arthur W. Burks (Box 6, Folder 110A)
  - Douglas Busch (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Douglas Busch (Box 6, Folder 111A)
  - C (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - "Cahiers pour L'Analyse" (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - "Cambridge University Reporter", 1954 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Sal Cannavo (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Thais Carter (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Centre for East Asian Studies, McGill University (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - C.C. Chang (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Isabelle C. Chang (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Pei-kai Chang (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - George Chatalian (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Chelsea Publishing Company (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Kitty Chen (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - L.S. Chen (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Ta-Tuan Chen, East Asian Linguistics Project (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Chung-yin Cheng (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - S.S. Chern (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Charles Chihara (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Chin (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - "China Now" (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - China, June-July 1972 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Chinese American Historical Biographical Project (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Chinese Delegation Visits (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Chinese Language (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Chinese Linguistics Conference, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Prabal Kanti Choudhury (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - K.L. Chow (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Christmas, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Alonzo Church (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Clarendon Press (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Juan Cobarrubias (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Bob Cohen (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Daniel Cohen, Eighth International Conference of Cybernetics and Systems (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - E.G.D. Cohen (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Paul J. Cohen (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - N.A. Coles (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Kathy Colleran (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Benjamin V.C. Collins (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Columbia University (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Completed Reprint Request Cards (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Computer Science Press (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Computers and Mathematics with Applications (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - "Computing in China: A Trip Report" (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Concept of Mind, Berkeley Meeting, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Conference on Methods in Philosophy and the Sciences (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Congress of Philosophy, August 1993 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Clarence M. Connelly (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Stephen Cook (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Rodney L. Cool, Memorial Tribute Program (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Joseph V. Cornacchio (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Cornell University Medical College (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence (Loose), 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Correspondence (Loose) (Box 8, Folder 163A)
  - John Cowles (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Craig, McNaughton, Bernays, Kalma'r, etc. (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Paul Cranefield (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Crank Mail (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Criticism of Bettelheim Publication (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - J.N. Crossley (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Current Letters (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - D (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Eberhard Dall'Asta (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Arthur C. Danto (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Jared L. Darlington (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - J. Dasrath (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Datebook, Oxford University, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Martin Davis (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Luiz Paulo de Alcantara (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Artur Demetrius (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Lloyd Demetrius (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - John Denes (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Daniel C. Dennett (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Daryn DeRose (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Marcus Dick (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Dictionary of International Biography (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Dictionary of American Scholars (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Vincent Dole (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Dover Publications (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Burton Dreben (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Thomas Drucker (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Michael Dummett (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Bradford Dunham (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Sam Dunnam (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - E (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - E (Box 9, Folder 194A)
  - John C. Eaton (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Editora Nacional (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Editorial Tecnos (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Edizioni di Filosofia e Scienze (Francesco del Franco) (Box 9, Folder 198)
  - Effort Reports (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Encyclopædia Britannica (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Encyclopedias (Box 9, Folder 201)
  - Engineering Sciences Course Descriptions [Harvard] (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Paul Ernest (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Etas Kompass (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - European Journal of Combinatorics (Box 9, Folder 205)
  - Shimon Even (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - F (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Wilma Fairbanks (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - W.D. Falk (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Solomon Feferman (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Gary Feinberg (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - William Feller (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Jens Erik Fenstad (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Craig Fields (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Fifth International Congress of Logic, Methodology and Philosophy of Science (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary of DNA and Avery, MacLeod and McCarty Paper, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 216)
  - Filing (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - First Chinese Linguistics Conference, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Roderick Firth (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Michael Fischer (Box 10, Folder 220)
  - Timothy B. Flannagan (Box 10, Folder 221)
  - Juliet Floyd (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Robert W. Floyd (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Jerry A. Fodor (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Dagfinn Føllesdal (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Franklin Ford (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Fourth Systems Symposium (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Harry Frankfurt (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - W.H. Freeman and Company Publishers (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - "The Fresman Seminar Program," a Report to the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1963, and "Recommendations on the Undergraduate Mathematics Program for Work in Computing," 1964, 1963, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - P. Friedland (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Harvey Friedman (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Ulf Friedrichsdorf (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - From Mathematics to Philosophy (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Fujita (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Fundamenta Mathematicae (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - G (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - G (Box 10, Folder 237A)
  - Robert M. Galatzer-Levy (Box 11, Folder 238)
  - Gale Research Inc. (Box 11, Folder 239)
  - Stephen Gale (Box 11, Folder 240)
  - Marián Gálik (Box 11, Folder 241)
  - Robin Gandy (Box 11, Folder 242)
  - Martin Garstens (Box 11, Folder 243)
  - James Geiser (Box 11, Folder 244)
  - General Motors Cancer Research Foundation (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Norman Geschwind (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - Roger Gibson (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Andrew M. Gleason (Box 11, Folder 248)
  - Warren Goldfarb (Box 11, Folder 249)
  - Walter Gottschalk (Box 11, Folder 250)
  - Grant SSF(7)-18, New York State Science and Technology Foundation (Box 11, Folder 251)
  - F.G. Gravalos (Box 11, Folder 252)
  - Lee W. Gregg (Box 11, Folder 253)
  - Nicholas Griffin (Box 11, Folder 254)
  - Marie Grossi (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 255)
  - Marie Grossi (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 256)
  - Otto Gschwandtner (Box 11, Folder 257)
  - J. Guberman (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation Application (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation Application (Box 11, Folder 259A)
  - H (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Peter Hacker (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - G.E.R. Haddock (Box 11, Folder 262)
  - Hagmann/Mitchell, Architects (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - David Harel (Box 11, Folder 264)
  - Lawrence Harper (Box 11, Folder 265)
  - Harper's Magazine (Box 11, Folder 266)
  - Harvard Club (Box 11, Folder 267)
  - Harvard Computing Center, General (Box 11, Folder 268)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Stål Aanderaa (Box 11, Folder 269)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Stål Aanderaa (Box 11, Folder 269A)
    Biographical / Historical
  - Harvard Correspondence, American Mathematical Society (Box 11, Folder 270)
  - Harvard Correspondence, American Mathematical Society (Box 11, Folder 270A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Michael P. Barnett (Box 12, Folder 271)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Michael P. Barnett (Box 12, Folder 271A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Bell Telephone Laboratories - Consulting, Project (Box 12, Folder 272)
  - Harvard Correspondence, R. Berger (Box 12, Folder 273)
  - Harvard Correspondence, R. Berger (Box 12, Folder 273A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Elwyn Berlekamp (Box 12, Folder 274)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Herbert J. Bohnert (Box 12, Folder 275)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Britannica Article (Box 12, Folder 276)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Kenneth R. Brown (Box 12, Folder 277)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Kenneth R. Brown (Box 12, Folder 277A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, R. Büchi (Box 12, Folder 278)
  - Harvard Correspondence, R. Büchi (Box 12, Folder 278A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Arthur W. Burks (Box 12, Folder 279)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Alan Cobham (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Alan Cobham (Box 12, Folder 280A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, S.A. Cook (Box 12, Folder 281)
  - Harvard Correspondence, S.A. Cook (Box 12, Folder 281A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Bradford Dunham (Box 12, Folder 282)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert R. Fenichel (Box 12, Folder 283)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert R. Fenichel (Box 12, Folder 283A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Michael Fischer (Box 12, Folder 284)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Michael Fischer (Box 12, Folder 284A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Patrick C. Fischer (Box 12, Folder 285)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Patrick C. Fischer (Box 12, Folder 285A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Joyce Friedman (Box 12, Folder 286)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Joyce Friedman (Box 12, Folder 286A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, David Fulton (Box 12, Folder 287)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Bernard A. Galler (Box 12, Folder 288)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John Egan Gibson (Box 12, Folder 289)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Sheila Greibach (Box 12, Folder 290)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Sheila Greibach (Box 12, Folder 290A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Peter Henrici (Box 12, Folder 291)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Peter Henrici (Box 12, Folder 291A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, C. Ward Henson (Box 12, Folder 292)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Philip K. Hooper (Box 12, Folder 293)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Philip K. Hooper (Box 12, Folder 293A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, IBM (Box 12, Folder 294)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Andrew Kahr (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Andrew Kahr (Box 12, Folder 295A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, M. Kochen (Box 12, Folder 296)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert T. Korfhage (Box 12, Folder 297)
  - Harvard Correspondence, G. Kreisel (Box 12, Folder 298)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Kenneth Krohn (Box 13, Folder 299)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Kenneth Krohn (Box 13, Folder 299A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Susumu Kumo (Box 13, Folder 300)
  - Harvard Correspondence, L (Box 13, Folder 301)
  - Harvard Correspondence, L (Box 13, Folder 301A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert A. Langevin (Box 13, Folder 302)
  - Harvard Correspondence, C.Y. Lee (Box 13, Folder 303)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Alan Lemmon (Box 13, Folder 304)
  - Harvard Correspondence, J.C.R. Licklider (Box 13, Folder 305)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Logic Colloquium, Oxford, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 306)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Eugene Luschi (Box 13, Folder 307)
  - Harvard Correspondence, M (Box 13, Folder 308)
  - Harvard Correspondence, M (Box 13, Folder 308A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, John McCarthy (Box 13, Folder 309)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Dean MacLaughlin (Box 13, Folder 310)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert F. McNaughton (Box 13, Folder 311)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Robert F. McNaughton (Box 13, Folder 311A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Richard J. Mansfield (Box 13, Folder 312)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Richard J. Mansfield (Box 13, Folder 312A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, David Martin (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Harvard Correspondence, David Martin (Box 13, Folder 313A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Leonard D. Massey, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 314)
  - Harvard Correspondence, George H. Mealy (Box 13, Folder 315)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Albert R. Meyer (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Albert R. Meyer (Box 13, Folder 316A)
  - Harvard Correspondence, Marvin Lee Minsky (Box 13, Folder 317)